Finding Aid for Varsinais-Suomi Region immigrant letters, 1880-1966
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Kustavi, letters to
  - Hilkka Lehtinen
    - From: Lena Mastin. Fla., 1965; 3 items (Reel 6)
  - Jalmari Palmroos
    - From: A. Matson. N.Y., 1961-1965; 3 items (Reel 6)
  - Uuno Santalahti
    - From: Risto Saarinen. Calif., 1951-1965; 10 items (Reel 6)
    - From: Hulda Sjoholm., 1956; 2 items (Reel 6)
  - Juhan Frisk
    - From: F. Simonson Ill., 1912; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Yrjö Salonen
    - From: Johan Suomi, Hilma Forstrom N.Y., Minn., 1964; 37 items (Reel 6)
  - Sanni Miettinen
    - From: various. N.Y., 1949; 3 items (Reel 6)
- Kuusisto, letters to
  - Gunnar Salminen
    - From: Kosti Salminen. Ont., 1962-1965; 2 items (Reel 6)
  - Elli Merivuori
    - From: Hjordis Jansson. Mass., 1957-1965; 18 items (Reel 6)
- Kuusjoki, letters to
  - Eino Saarela
    - From: Jussi Saarela. Brazil, 1938-1963; 50 items (Reel 6)
- Laitila, letters to
  - August Nurmi
    - From: Vihtor Nurmi. Minn., Wash., 1916-1921; 3 items (Reel 6)
  - Armas Tuominen
    - From: Miina Nurmi. N.Y., 1907; 2 items (Reel 6)
    - From: Arvo Tuomi. Ont., 1964-1965; 2 items (Reel 6)
  - Olga Rosten
    - From: Amanda Pajander. Calif., 1935; 2 items (Reel 6)
  - Irene Haahtinen
    - From: Mary Larsen. N.Y., 1940-1963; 3 items (Reel 6)
    - From: Hilma Freeman. Calif., 1940-1945; 2 items (Reel 6)
    - From: Gustaf Vaivio. New Zealand, Wash., Minn., Calif., 1914-1923; 7 items (Reel 6)
  - Hilma Aerila
    - From: August Aalto. Calif., 1906-1907; 4 items (Reel 6)
    - From: Bert Aalto. Minn., 1911; 4 items (Reel 6)
    - From: Einar Laurila. Minn., 1911-1919; 5 items (Reel 6)
  - Rauha Tuominen
    - From: Sylvia Korh. Wash., 1966; 2 items (Reel 6)
  - Sirkka Haahtinen
    - From: Aina Koskinen. Finland, B.C., 1907-1966; 2 items (Reel 6)
  - Saima Koskirinta
    - From: Aino Heisholt. Ont., 1962; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Alma Heinonen
    - From: questionnaire only. (Reel 6)
    - From: Maria Raunio. N.Y., 1915; 2 items (Reel 6)
  - Ellilja Vierumäki
    - From: Olga Vierumaki. Mass., N.Y., 1919-1922; 5 items (Reel 6)
  - Taimi Nurmelin
    - From: Sanni Airo. N.J., 1952; 2 items (Reel 6)
  - T. Valtanen
    - From: Oskar Nummelin., 1958; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Juho Nummelin
    - From: Kosti Nummelin. Nova Scotia, 1928; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Juho Jarvinen
    - From: Jalmari Jarvinen. Negaunee, Mich., 1911-1934; 9 items (Reel 7)
  - Elma Tuomi
    - From: Selma Vainio. N.Y., 1912; 1 items (Reel 7)
    - From: Arvo Rintanen. Ont., 1966; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Senja Hemmilä
    - From: Selma Kuusela. photos, 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Vihtor Vainio
    - From: Selma Kuusela., undated; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Olga Saarnio
    - From: Frans Silvan. Wash., 1963; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Kaarina Laihonen
    - From: Naimi Norman. N.Y., 1939; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Olga Jokinen
    - From: Olga Mäkilä. Quebec, 1934; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Taimi Hällynen
    - From: Lempi Sodergren. Mass., 1963; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Aina Rantavainio
    - From: Olga Kultalahti. N.Y., 1960-1963; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Markku Leino
    - From: Walfrid Rosten. Minn., 1963; 11 items (Reel 7)
  - Kustaa Leppä
    - From: Suoma Tuominen. Wash., Manitoba., 1965-1966; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Väinö Knaapila
    - From: Hilda Pajari. Quebec, Ont., 1946-1965; 6 items (Reel 7)
  - Artturi Suominen
    - From: Laila Carlson. N.Y., 1959-1961; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Kai Rosten
    - From: Milja Rosten. Que., 1966; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Katri Lylander
    - From: Armas Lylander. Australia, Japan, Singapore, 1956-1963; 5 items (Reel 7)
  - Waldemar Sunila
    - From: Ruuno Sunila. photo, 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Aili Aaltonen
    - From: Aino Vainio., 1965; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Niilo Hautamäki
    - From: Hilma Warjonen. Wash., Minn., 1908-1965; 6 items (Reel 7)
  - Rauha Laine
    - From: Martha Laine. N.Y., 1947-1951; 10 items (Reel 7)
  - Hilja Lainio
    - From: Seppo Lainio. Australia, 1960; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Kustaa Lehtonen
    - From: Sandra Saari. Minn., N.Y., 1961-1965; 4 items (Reel 7)
  - Jenny Linden
    - From: various. N.Y., Spain, 1956-1969; 11 items (Reel 7)
  - Ida Suikkila
    - From: Lempi Bergsten. N.J., 1945-1966; 30 items (Reel 7)
    - From: Andy Hill. Oregon. N.J., 1956-1965; 12 items (Reel 7)
    - From: A. Inkeri. Conn., 1961-1965; 6 items (Reel 7)
    - From: Mr. Niemi. from the ship, Conn., 1960-1962; 6 items (Reel 7)
  - Irja Vainio
    - From: Sender Unknown. N.Y., 1951; 1 items (Reel 7)
- Lemu, letters to
  - Kosti Alin
    - From: Otto Mailanen. Calif., 1928; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Lauri Vallunen
    - From: Juho Tuomola. photo, 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Anni Mattila
    - From: Altti Lehto. Maine, 1947-1948; 4 items (Reel 7)
- Lieto, letters to
  - Ester Wanhalinna
    - From: Kalle Salonen, Ines Salonen. Sweden, Fla., 1947-1966; 30 items (Reel 7)
  - Kaarlo Halme
    - From: Kaarlo Halme. photos, 14 items (Reel 7)
  - Toivo Tähtinen
    - From: Toivo Tahtinen. photos, 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Taimi Heikkilä
    - From: Rauha Ojala. Wash., 1924; 1 items (Reel 7)
    - From: Hella Ojala. Kaleva, Mich., 1948-1949; 5 items (Reel 7)
  - Alma Pelttari
    - From: Anna Wirta. questionnaire only. (Reel 7)
  - Taavetti Lusto
    - From: Taavetti Lusto. questionnaire only. (Reel 7)
- Loimaa, letters to
  - Nikolai Nurmi
    - From: Conrad Ranta. Minn., 1941-1952; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Helga Tamminen
    - From: Mari Laine. photos, 10 items (Reel 7)
  - Eevi Saarenpää
    - From: Amanda Junnila. Mass., 1961-1965; 9 items (Reel 7)
  - Antti Kuusela
    - From: Aino Kuparinen. Quebec, Ont., N.Y., Maine, 1956-1965; 31 items (Reel 7)
- Lokalahti, letters to
  - Ruth Laaksonen
    - From: various. N.Y., 1937-1954; 4 items (Reel 7)
  - Lempi Salonen
    - From: Olga Kivisto
      - N.Y., 1913; 1 items (Reel 7)
      - Baltic, Mich., South Range, Mich., 1909-1947; 2 items (Reel 7)
      - N.Y., 1948; 1 items (Reel 7)
      - South Range, Mich., 1952-1969; 7 items (Reel 7)
      - N.Y., 1965; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Olga Luotonen
    - From: Olga Erickson Calif., 1956-1966; 5 items (Reel 7)
    - From: Taimi Laaksonen. Fla., 1964-1966; 4 items (Reel 7)
  - Väinö Kittilä
    - From: Alina Sundquist. questionnaire only. (Reel 7)
  - J. Alkio
    - From: various. Calif., 1933-1960s; 17 items (Reel 7)
  - Vieno Kulmala
    - From: Sender Unknown. N.Y., 1907; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Town of Lokalahti
    - From: Alli Sundsvall. N.J., 1965; 1 items (Reel 7)
- Maaria, letters to
  - Martta Setälä
    - From: Alpo Setala. Fla., 1961-1965; 4 items (Reel 7)
    - From: Elsa Setala. Mass., 1953; 1 items (Reel 7)
    - From: Kustaa Setala. Oregon., 1953-1969 (Reel 7)
    - From: Leena Wahlstedt. Mass., 1962; 2 items (Reel 7)
    - From: John Setala. Ill., 1956-1957; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Hilkka Salmenoja
    - From: Maria Peterson., 1964; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Anja Halme
    - From: Alli Anttila. England, from the ship, Australia, 1959-1962; 4 items (Reel 7)
  - Margareta Osterman
    - From: Eine Matikainen. Australia, 1961-1962; 13 items (Reel 7)
    - From: Eine Matikainen. Australia, 1962-1966; 6 items (Reel 8)
- Marttila, letters to
  - Väinö Aarnio
    - From: Werner Joki. R.I., 1947; 2 items (Reel 8)
    - From: Hilda Kronval. Watton, Mich., 1946-1952; 7 items (Reel 8)
- Masku, letters to
  - Amanda Grönholm
    - From: Heikki Gronholm
      - Mass., Conn., N.Y., Wis., 1908-1912; 30 items (Reel 8)
      - Ironwood, Mich., 1912; 6 items (Reel 8)
      - Calif., 1938-1956; 7 items (Reel 8)
    - From: Mari Wainio
      - N.Y., Conn., N.J., Ill., Wis., 1909-1912; 22 items (Reel 8)
      - Iron Mountain, Mich., Marquette, Mich., 1952-1953; 4 items (Reel 8)
  - Uuno Kaipe
    - From: Pauli Gronholm
      - Anvil, Mich., 1914-1915; 4 items (Reel 8)
      - N.Y., 1931-1952; 4 items (Reel 8)
  - Sylvi Grönholm
    - From: Lauri Holm. Ohio, 1941-1954; 3 items (Reel 8)
- Merimasku, letters to
  - Oskar Luotonen
    - From: Oskar Luotonen. Wyo., 1928; 5 items (Reel 8)
  - Yrjö Laaksonen
    - From: Katri Andersson. N.Y., N.J., Conn., Fla., 1938-1961; 28 items (Reel 8)
- Mietoinen, letters to
  - Fiina Lehtonen
    - From: Ida Lindell. N.Y., Calif., 1894-1950; 33 items (Reel 8)
  - Alina Ohman
    - From: Fredrik Johansson. Tex., Pa., 1927-1940; 20 items (Reel 8)
    - From: Leonard Fagerlund. Fla., 1962-1965; 9 items (Reel 8)
- Muurla, letters to
  - Elvi Seppälä
    - From: E.J. Cerank. N.Y., 1961; 16 items (Reel 8)
  - Alma Lehtonen
    - From: Aksia Karkinen. from the ship, Conn., 1958-1966; 52 items (Reel 8)
  - Kyllikki Järvinen
    - From: Hilma Hilden. Calif., 1958-1959; 12 items (Reel 8)
  - Aino Risu
    - From: Milja Tiitson. photos, 7 items (Reel 8)
  - Dagmar Packalen
    - From: Hilda Virtanen. Que., 1963-1965; 17 items (Reel 8)
  - Kerttu Vuorinen
    - From: Sisko Blid. B.C., 1957-1962; 10 items (Reel 8)
- Mynämäki, letters to
  - Irene Haanperä
    - From: Elsa Nelson. N.J., 1952-1956; 16 items (Reel 8)
    - From: Elsa Nelson. N.J. Photos., 1952-1956; 20 items (Reel 9)
  - Mrs. Hattinen
    - From: Arvo Nurmi. Midland, Mich., 1966; 5 items (Reel 9)
  - Mrs. Ahlgren
    - From: Erkki Soininen. Australia, 1966; 1 items (Reel 9)
- Naantali, letters to
  - Aili Kurala
    - From: J.E. Lillback. Lulu, Gardner. N.Y., 1929; 11 items (Reel 9)
- Oripää, letters to
  - Eevi Jokinen
    - From: Vilho Tuomisto. Minn., 1964; 4 items (Reel 9)
  - Sylvi Uusitalo
    - From: Matti. Syrjdnen. Minn., 1961-1963; 3 items (Reel 9)
  - Katri Kaloniemi
    - From: Helena Hendrickson. Conn., 1960-1966; 8 items (Reel 9)
  - Aliisa Lehtonen
    - From: Emilia Andersson. Minn., 1961-1962; 4 items (Reel 9)
  - Eukarius Leino
    - From: Emilia Andersson. Minn., 1965-1966; 12 items (Reel 9)
  - Saara Tuomi
    - From: Aimo Tuomi. Pa., 1964; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Aili Mlkelä
    - From: Jalmar Jaakola. Fla., Mass., 1947-1964; 4 items (Reel 9)
  - Pekka Keloniemi
    - From: Antti Klemetti. Ont., 1954-1962; 5 items (Reel 9)
- Paattinen, letters to
  - Viljo Houni
    - From: Helena Ikavalko. Ont., 1953-1965; 5 items (Reel 9)
- Paimio, letters to
  - Elli Pennanen
    - From: Ina Haino. N.Y., 1951-1962; 2 items (Reel 9)
  - Katri Neva
    - From: Eeva Sjogren. R.I., 1964-1966; 2 items (Reel 9)
- Parainen, letters to
  - Fredrik Wennerström
    - From: Gunnar Wannerstrom. N.Y., 1963-1966; 10 items (Reel 9)
- Perniö, letters to
  - Leonard Soisalo
    - From: Selma Soisalo. Mass., 1963-1966; 4 items (Reel 9)
  - Ada Ruohonen
    - From: Rakel Hangcok. New Zea, 1958-1966; 124 items (Reel 9)
    - From: Rauni Cranforth. New Zea, 1958-1961; 101 items (Reel 9)
    - From: Rauni Cranforth. New Zealand, Ont., Denmark, 1959-1966; 302 items (Reel 10)
  - Signe Bergroth
    - From: Eino Bergroth. Ont., 1964-1965; 8 items (Reel 10)
  - Sigrid Ahlquist
    - From: Kalle Ahlquist. Ont.,1961-1966, 11 items (Reel 10)
  - Tilda Sirkiä
    - From: Sakari Sirkia. Australia, 1965; 2 items (Reel 10)
- Pertteli, letters to
  - Rauha Ketola
    - From: Alma Kuusela. Calif., 1945; 1 items (Reel 10)
- Pyhämaa, letters to
  - Lea Lehtonen
    - From: Alina Ylitalo. Oregon., Wash., 1908-1924; 8 items (Reel 10)
  - Onni Pussila
    - From: J. Suprenant. Wash., 1949-1955; 7 items (Reel 10)
    - From: Gustaf Sevon. Mass., Minn., Wash., 1909; 6 items (Reel 10)
  - Ellen Pussila
    - From: Emma Poyla. Calif., 1950-1969; 4 items (Reel 10)
    - From: Kust Poyla. Calif., 1937; 2 items (Reel 10)
    - From: Hilda Poyla. Calif., 1937-1938; 3 items (Reel 10)
  - Aina Siivonen
    - From: Teodor Siivonen. Wash., 1907-1945; 17 items (Reel 10)
    - From: Lyydia Fredriksson. Wash., 1915-1951; 8 items (Reel 10)
  - Olga Lehtinen
    - From: Harry Walden. N.Y., 1938-1949; 8 items (Reel 10)
  - Jenny Tuominen
    - From: Johan Tuominen. Argentina, 1911; 2 items (Reel 10)
  - Almi Mikola
    - From: Oiva Nurmisto. N.Y., Calif, England, Belgium, Mass., Ore., 1921-1924; 25 items (Reel 10)
    - From: Oiva Nurmisto. N.Y., Wash., Calif., 1926-1948; 61 items (Reel 11)
  - Aina Viljanen
    - From: Hilda Harjula. N.Y., 1925-1965; 20 items (Reel 11)
  - Fanny Hautanen
    - From: Vilma Lehto. N.Y., 1949-1965; 10 items (Reel 11)
  - Väinö Kivel
    - From: Frans Lehtonen. Mass., 1965; 6 items (Reel 11)
  - Signe Nissilä
    - From: Juho Nissila. Sweden, N.Y., Conn., N.J., 1906-1919; 19 items (Reel 11)
    - From: Vihtori Salmi.
      - Manistique, Mich., 1905-1906; 8 items (Reel 11)
      - Minn., Ind., Pa., 1906-1964; 93 items (Reel 11)
  - Signe Nissilä
    - From: Tilda Palm
      - Fin, 1906; 2 items (Reel 11)
      - Atlantic, Mich., 1906; 3 items (Reel 11)
      - N.Y., Ind., N.J., Minn., B.C., Wis., 1906-1963; 66 items (Reel 11)
  - Aili Pellonperä
    - From: various.
      - St. Ignace, Mich., 1947; 1 items (Reel 11)
      - D. C., 1948; 3 items (Reel 11)
      - St. Ignace, Mich., Livonia, Mich., 1948-1964; 24 items (Reel 11)
  - Paavo Mäki
    - From: Anton Maki. Minn., 1910-1963; 10 items (Reel 11)
  - Matti Vauranoja
    - From: J.Siren. Ont., 1908; 1 items (Reel 11)
  - Matti Vauranoja
    - From: Lauri Vauranoja. Finland, Minn., S.D., 1913-1916; 19 items (Reel 11)
    - From: Lauri Vauranoja. Minn., S.D., 1917-1929; 32 items (Reel 12)
  - Eina Murto
    - From: Ida Vesanen. Conn., R.I., 1921-1966; 30 items (Reel 12)
  - Elma Laine
    - From: Hilma Williams. N.J., 1938-1963; 17 items (Reel 12)
  - Naimi Saarto
    - From: Irja Brown. Conn., Calif., 1947-1957; 23 items (Reel 12)
- Rymättylä, letters to
  - Alli Koisaari
    - From: Felix Fagerroos. Fla., 1928-1936; 50 items (Reel 12)
  - Hilda Aaltonen
    - From: Karl Leinonen. Mass., N.J., 1900-1957; 10 items (Reel 12)
    - From: Almira Pietila. Mass., 1965; 3 items (Reel 12)
    - From: Kustaa Karlsson. photos, 2 items (Reel 12)
    - From: Kalle Nummelin., undated; 1 items (Reel 12)
  - Aino Tähti
    - From: Eeli Virtanen. Ohio, 1948-1952; 2 items (Reel 12)
    - From: Ella Virtanen. Ohio, 1948-1953; 3 items (Reel 12)
    - From: Fredrik Virtanen. Australia, 1948; 1 items (Reel 12)
  - Lydia Lehtinen
    - From: Feodor Lehtinen. Minn., 1906; 2 items (Reel 12)
  - A. Kurala
    - From: Arthur Lindholm. N.Y., Eng, 1906-1920; 3 items (Reel 12)
    - From: Kustaa Lindqvist. Calif., 1954-1955; 4 items (Reel 12)
  - Kerttu Lähteenmäki
    - From: Ainolf Kurala. Calif., 1912; 4 items (Reel 12)
    - From: Aili Kurala. N.Y., Fla., 1923-1965; 129 items (Reel 12)
    - From: Alli Lindholm. N.Y., 1926-1936; 20 items (Reel 12)
  - Recipient Unknown
    - From: Albin Nurmi. Calif., 1909; 1 items (Reel 12)
    - From: Jalmar Liljeroos., 1910; 1 items (Reel 12)
    - From: Vivi Aho. N.Y., 1911; 1 items (Reel 12)
    - From: Kalle Nummelin. Calif., 1910; 1 items (Reel 12)
    - From: Sender Unknown. N.Y., England, Calif., 1907-1916; 21 items (Reel 12)
- Sauvo, letters to
  - Elli Valtamo
    - From: Martha Anttila. Wis., 1931-1949; 4 items (Reel 12)
    - From: Martha Anttila. Wis., 1951-1956; 10 items (Reel 13)
- Somero, letters to
  - Lea Similä
    - From: Arvo Simila. Man., 1965-1966; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Olavi Mäkinen
    - From: Hilda Albertson. Fla., 1963-1964; 3 items (Reel 13)
- Suomusjärvi, letters to
  - Recipient Unknown
    - From: Kalle Hepomaki. questionnaire only. (Reel 13)
  - Alfhild Terho
    - From: Sven Granholm. Sweden, 1961; 3 items (Reel 13)
- Taivassalo, letters to
  - Jalmari Päivärinta
    - From: Ida Ahlberg. photo, 1 items (Reel 13)
    - From: Kaisa Sjoblom. Oregon., 1953-1957; 4 items (Reel 13)
  - Katri Rantanen
    - From: E. Lehtonen. N.Y., 1950-1964; 9 items (Reel 13)
    - From: H. Lindroth. N.Y., 1957; 1 items (Reel 13)
    - From: V. Williams. N.Y., 1958; 1 items (Reel 13)
    - From: Helmi Huhtala
      - N.Y., 1949-1959; 6 items (Reel 13)
      - Ont., 1964; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Oskar Mattila
    - From: Henry Suominen. Maine, 1903; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Vieno Osterman
    - From: Anna Roiha. Iron River, Mich. (Reel 13)
  - Meeri Rytsälä
    - From: Ilma Hillberg. N.Y., Calif., 1905-1951; 10 items (Reel 13)
  - Toivo Vehanen
    - From: Anton Simantson. questionnaire only. (Reel 13)
    - From: Nikolai Vehanen. questionnaire only. (Reel 13)
    - From: Hilma Vehanen. questionnaire only. (Reel 13)
    - From: Ellen Vehanen. N.Y., 1966; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Pentti Palletvuori
    - From: Ilma Laakso. Ohio, 1953-1965; 18 items (Reel 13)
  - Hulda Vuorinen
    - From: Albin Leino. Calif., 1945; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Betty Tainio
    - From: Sanni Karppinen., undated; 4 items (Reel 13)
  - Lempi Elomaa
    - Photos, 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Sairna Tukkinen
    - From: Nikolai Makitalo. Conn., 1951-1965; 14 items (Reel 13)
  - Anna Kleernola
    - From: Aino Kosonen. N.Y., 1965; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Recipient Unknown
    - From: Eino Paavola. photos, 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Fanny Hasula
    - From: Sender Unknown. Ont., 1965; 3 items (Reel 13)
    - From: Margit Ayrento., undated; 1 items (Reel 13)
    - From: Katri Sjoblom., undated; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Bertta Puonti
    - From: Martta Diduch. Ont., 1965; 5 items (Reel 13)
  - V. Veistinen
    - From: Mrs. Mattila. N.Y., 1916-1965; 6 items (Reel 13)
  - Yrjö Koskinen
    - From: Martta Koskinen. Me., 1960-1963; 8 items (Reel 13)
  - Väinö Salovaara
    - From: Eino Salovaara. Ont., 1962; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Siiri Sandholm
    - From: Elvi Jalonen., undated; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Impi Salomaa
    - From: Ragnhild Suvakko. photos, 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Eero Einiö
    - Official papers, 14 items (Reel 13)
- Tarvasjoki, letters to
  - Taimi Tahila
    - From: Paavo Junnila. photos, 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Juho Mäki
    - From: Juho Maki. photos, 12 items (Reel 13)
  - Anna Tahila
    - From: Kalle Tahila. Minn., 1905-1962; 27 items (Reel 13)
    - From: Jussi Hakamaki. Minn., Fla., 1938-1965; 33 items (Reel 13)
    - From: Olga Piirainen. Calif, Minn., Wash. (Reel 13)
    - From: Anna Nygard. Minn., 1917-1965; 54 items (Reel 13)
  - Fiina Lehtinen
    - From: Anna Nygard. Minn., 1914-1969; 25 items (Reel 13)
    - From: Anna Nygard. Pa., Minn., 1960-1966; 42 items (Reel 14)
  - Viljo Laine
    - From: Frank Hill. Minn., 1906-1963; 5 items (Reel 14)
  - Kalle Ihamäki
    - Bank book, photos, 3 items (Reel 14)
  - Esteri Heinonen
    - From: Kustaa Kylanpaa. photos, 4 items (Reel 14)
  - Ester Kankare
    - From: Paul Junnila. Cornell, Mich., 1961-1962; 4 items (Reel 14)
  - Kirsti Lehtonen
    - From: Niilo Niemi. Ont., Fla., 1946; 1930-1964; 22 items (Reel 14)
- Turku, letters to
  - Saima Pursimo
    - From: various. N.Y., Minn., England, Finland, Spain, 1904-1906; 17 items (Reel 14)
  - Recipient Unknown
    - From: various. Ireland, N.Y., 1899-1954; 15 items (Reel 14)
  - Salli Lahti
    - From: Selim Hedlund, Efraim Hedlund. Finland, Eng, 1891-1961; 23 items (Reel 14)
  - Anni Nakolinna
    - From: Juho Knaapi. Ont., 1919-1945; 9 items (Reel 14)
  - Aini Ruusuvaara
    - From: Alfrid Ahlfors. Argentina, Wash., Minn., W.Va., N.Y., 1913-1926 (Reel 14)
  - A. Laine
    - From: Hilja Wuori. Minn., Fla., 1922-1964 (Reel 14)
  - Aino Laine
    - From: Frans Hurmerinta. Minn., Wis., 1909-1964; 8 items (Reel 14)
  - Martti Toivonen
    - From: Almi Toivonen. N.Y., 1950-1965; 11 items (Reel 14)
  - Hilda Aarnio
    - From: Sender Unknown. N.H., N.Y., 1920; 3 items (Reel 14)
- Uskela, letters to
  - Ellida Anttila
    - From: Beda Forssell. Mass., 1930-1965; 7 items (Reel 14)
  - Juho Koivusaari
    - From: Akseli Sankari. Fla., 1955-1961; 7 items (Reel 14)
  - Viola Omeri
    - From: Helena Launoja. Fla., 1958-1962; 4 items (Reel 14)
  - Aino Nikkanen
    - From: Elvi Reiman. Soviet Union, 1954-1969; 5 items (Reel 14)
    - From: Kerttu Kirjavainen. Australia, 1964-1966; 25 items (Reel 14)
  - Kaarina Mäkinen
    - From: Martta Hiitola., undated; 1 items (Reel 14)
  - Gunnar Mäkinen
    - From: Mirjam Oksa. N.Y., 1952-1964; 6 items (Reel 14)
- Vehmaa, letters to
  - Anna Tuomola
    - From: John Wall. N.Y., undated; 2 items (Reel 14)
  - Sylvi Manner
    - From: Oscar Hackley. Minn., 1960-1965; 4 items (Reel 14)
  - Juho Leino
    - From: Sanni Leino. Mass., 1911; 2 items (Reel 14)
  - Arvo Leino
    - From: Saima Hendrickson. Calif., 1945; 2 items (Reel 14)
    - From: Albin Leino. Calif., 1939; 1 items (Reel 14)
  - Alli Virtala
    - From: Amanda Lindberg. questionnaire only. (Reel 14)
    - From: Amanda Lindberg. N.Y., 1963-1965; 4 items (Reel 15)
  - Veera Paajanen
    - From: Hilta Tiainen. questionnaire only. (Reel 15)
  - Vihtori Virtanen
    - From: Olga Johnson. Wash., 1945-1962; 10 items (Reel 15)
  - Alma Koivisto
    - From: Santeri Lehto. Russia, Ont., N.J., D.C., Miss., N.Y., 1915-1930; 22 items (Reel 15)
  - Toini Puttaa
    - From: Line Martin. Fla., 1961-1966; 10 items (Reel 15)
    - From: Sonia Gomez. N.Y., 1946-1962; 7 items (Reel 15)
  - Martta Manen
    - From: Hilda Suominen. Wis., 1913-1965; 25 items (Reel 15)
  - Maria Sainio
    - From: Eine Sundstrom. N.Y., Mass., Conn., 1920-1963; 37 items (Reel 15)
  - Paavo Saarinen
    - From: Leonard Fagerlund. Fla., 1963-1964; 3 items (Reel 15)
  - Kyösti Karvonen
    - From: Erkki Karvonen. Sweden, 1966; 1 items (Reel 15)
  - Aino Rantanen
    - From: Mirja Rantanen. photos, 2 items (Reel 15)
  - Olavi Isomäki
    - From: Jenny Nissinen, Hilkka Carlson. N.Y., 1953-1969; 18 items (Reel 15)
- Velkua, letters to
  - Aimo Ilmalahti
    - From: Tekla Ingman. B.C., Calif, Alaska, 1931-1940; 10 items (Reel 15)
- Västanfjärd, letters to
  - Sofia Bernstedt
    - From: Alexander Börman. Calif., Alta., Mont., 1922-1927; 10 items (Reel 15)
    - From: Albert Börman. England, N.Y., 1912-1917; 6 items (Reel 15)
  - Agda Karlsson
    - From: Oskar Lagerstrom. Calif., 1945-1948; 52 items (Reel 15)
  - Sally Lindroos
    - From: Amandus Lindroos. photos, 2 items (Reel 15)
  - Robert Fagerström
    - From: Ben Smith. N.Y., 1955-1965; 19 items (Reel 15)
  - Helena Henriksson
    - From: Axel Börman., undated; 4 items (Reel 15)
    - From: Erik Forsstrom. N.Y., N.J., 1903-1951; 4 items (Reel 15)
    - From: Irene Caven. N.Y., 1946; 1 items (Reel 15)
    - From: Dagmar Bowen. Eng, 1950-1961; 4 items (Reel 15)
  - Agnes Sjösten
    - From: August Borman. Alta., 1929-1965; 8 items (Reel 15)
  - Recipient Unknown
    - From: Johan Ginlund, Karl Ginlund. N.Y., 1911-1959; 3 items (Reel 15)
  - Anna Jaakola
    - From: Anna Litz. Dakota, 1914; 5 items (Reel 15)
    - From: Margit Ditman., 1914; 3 items (Reel 15)
  - Saima Arell
    - From: Hjalmar Abrahamsson. N.Y., 1955; 5 items (Reel 15)
  - Evert Sundvik
    - From: Sigurd Karlsson. N.Y., 1926-1927; 4 items (Reel 15)
  - Anna Henriksson
    - From: various., undated; 10 items (Reel 15)
  - Lydia Ahlstrand
    - From: August Sundberg. Ill., Calif., 1925-1948; 6 items (Reel 15)
    - From: Berta Sundberg. China, 1921-1928; 11 items (Reel 15)
    - From: Valdemar Andsten, Edvin Andsten. New Brunswick, Guam, N.Y., 1925-1958; 33 items (Reel 15)
  - Konrad Sundström)
    - Photos, 2 items (Reel 15)
  - Hjördis Björman
    - From: Lennart Borman. N.J., Panama, N.Y., Conn., 1923-1930; 9 items (Reel 15)
  - Gunnel Björkman
    - From: Herbert Abrahamson. Ont., 1922-1956; 3 items (Reel 15)
  - Gotthelm Mickelsson
    - Photos, 6 items (Reel 15)
    - Passport, 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Karin Lindström
    - From: Elis Lindstrom. Calif., 1937-1954; 6 items (Reel 16)
  - Arvid Carlen
    - Photos, 6 items (Reel 16)
  - Aina Sandberg
    - From: Dagny Sandberg. N.Y., Mass., 1939-1965; 19 items (Reel 16)
  - Recipient Unknown
    - From: Karl Mollgren. questionnaire only. (Reel 16)
- Yläne, letters to
  - Pauli Suominen
    - From: Johan Reinvall., 1878-1892; 5 items (Reel 16)
  - Ossi Mäki-Laurila
    - From: Edla Vehanen. Minn., 1904-1911; 2 items (Reel 16)
  - Juho Ojala
    - From: Sigrid Vuorinen, John Tulonen.
      - Wash., 1912-1935; 10 items (Reel 16)
      - Ontonagon, Mich., 1946; 1 items (Reel 16)
  - Saima Lukkala
    - From: Hilja Anderson. Conn., 1934-1966; 16 items (Reel 16)